
    [
        {
            "id": 0,
            "Question": "Commonly used data types DO NOT include:",
            "CorrectAnswer": "C",
            "A": "strings",
            "B": "booleans",
            "C": "alerts",
            "D": "numbers"
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "Question": "The condition in an if / else statement is enclosed within ____.",
            "CorrectAnswer": "C",
            "A": "quotes",
            "B": "curly brackets",
            "C": "parentheses",
            "D": "square brackets"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "Question": "Arrays in JavaScript can be used to store ____.",
            "CorrectAnswer": "D",
            "A": "numbers and strings",
            "B": "other arrays",
            "C": "booleans",
            "D": "all of the above"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "Question": "String values must be enclosed within ____ when being assigned to variables.",
            "CorrectAnswer": "C",
            "A": "commas",
            "B": "curly brackets",
            "C": "quotes",
            "D": "parentheses"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "Question": "A very useful tool used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:",
            "CorrectAnswer": "D",
            "A": "JavaScript",
            "B": "terminal / bash",
            "C": "for loops",
            "D": "console.log"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "Question": "Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?",
            "CorrectAnswer": "C",
            "A": "JavaScript is is complementary to and integrated with HTML.",
            "B": "JavaScript is open and cross-platform.",
            "C": "Both of the above.",
            "D": "None of the above"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "Question": "Which of the following type of variable takes precedence over other if names are same?",
            "CorrectAnswer": "B",
            "A": "global variable",
            "B": "local variable",
            "C": "Both of the above.",
            "D": "None of the above"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "Question": "Which built-in method returns the characters in a string beginning at the specified location?",
            "CorrectAnswer": "A",
            "A": "substr()",
            "B": "getSubstring()",
            "C": "slice()",
            "D": "None of the above."
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "Question": "Which of the following function of String object executes the search for a match between a regular expression and a specified string?",
            "CorrectAnswer": "D",
            "A": "concat()",
            "B": "match()",
            "C": "replace()",
            "D": "search()"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "Question": "Which of the following function of String object returns the calling string value converted to upper case while respecting the current locale?",
            "CorrectAnswer": "A",
            "A": "toLocaleUpperCase()",
            "B": "toUpperCase()",
            "C": "toString()",
            "D": "substring()"
        }
        
]